MOHAMMAD AHMADIAN HONARMAND

Address:

No. 8, Magidie St, Resalat Blvd, Tehran

Phone:

+98 921 51 66 403

Email:

Ahmadian@expertmql4.ir

Summary

Mql programmer, expert builder and indicator of stock and futures market. Python programmer, build auxiliary tools in the stock market, Using artificial intelligence and deep learning and supervised learning.

Skill Highlights

- Python programming
- MQL programming
- C ++ programming
- Trading in the stock market
- Making experts and indicators
- Web design
- Deep learning

Education

- Bachelor of Electrical Engineering, Qom University of Technology
- Bachelor student of computer at Payame Noor University of Tehran
- Financial Markets Trading Specialist (Stock Exchange)

Languages

- English
- Persian

Experience

- Internet Café-Part time(2015-2016)
- Building electrical-Part time(2016-2019)
- Accounting-Part time(2018-2019)
- Freelancer-MQL5.com(2020)
- Expert seller and indicator-MQL5.com(2020)

Site: expertmql4.ir

Date of birth: 1996.11.04

Job: Manufacturer of experts and indicators in the stock market